You know, Joe?
你知道吗 Joe？
I think we've put these students enough in a tangent with the tsunami and
我觉得这些学生接触 Tsunami 和 Digifield
the digifield apps, right?
应用已经够多了 对吧？
&gt;&gt; Well, I think it was a necessary tangent.
— 是的 而且 我认为这种接触也很有必要
There's a lot of concepts and
在 Android 应用中 有太多概念
code changes that make an HTTP request work in an Android app.
和代码更改可以让 HTTP 请求工作了
&gt;&gt; Yeah, that's totally true.
— 没错 完全正确
&gt;&gt; I didn't want to make the student copy and
— 我不希望学生只是 机械地复制和粘贴
paste a bunch of code that they didn't understand.
他们根本不懂的 一堆代码
You guys don't want that, right?
你也不希望这样 对吧?
&gt;&gt; Okay, well I think they've got a hang of it now.
— 是的 而且我认为 他们现在已经掌握了这些知识
They've been through a lot of concepts, they've done a bunch of quiz questions
他们已学过诸多概念 也做过了一堆测验问题
and they've don a little bit of coding, too.
而且还做了一点 编码
But now it's time for the real challenge.
但当下才是 真正的挑战
Where they can see whether or
也就是见证他们能不能
not they can apply all of that to the Quake Report app.
将全部所学运用到 Quake Report 应用中
&gt;&gt; Yes, we want you to apply everything that you've learned in the last two
— 是的 我们希望你能将 在前两节课中的全部所学
lessons so far to the Quake Report app.
运用到 Quake Report 应用中
Instead of using a hardcoded JSON response, perform an HTTP
而不是使用硬编码的 JSON 响应 对我们在
request to a given query URL that we provide in part of the response and
响应部分提供的指定查询 URL 执行 HTTP 请求并
display it in the list.
将其显示在列表中
&gt;&gt; So in this quiz, you're going to right down a plan for
— 因此 在此测验中 你需要写下一个方案
the list of changes you need to make to the app.
列出你要对应用 作出的更改
But no need to make the changes yet.
但当前无需执行更改
&gt;&gt; There's no right or wrong answer,
— 答案没有对错之分
just write down notes to help you as you start to think of the problem.
只是写下注释 在开始 思考问题时为你提供帮助
&gt;&gt; Yeah, totally you know,
— 是的 而且你知道的
if your mind goes blank, don't worry it happens to the best of us.
思维陷入空白 并没有什么好担心的 我们也经常发生这种情况
&gt;&gt; This is good real world practice when you're asked to work on
— 当让你从事一项 无从下手的工作时
something you have no idea where to start.
可谓是考验你实践 应用能力的良机
&gt;&gt; Yeah, so
— 是的 所以
take the time to resituate yourself in the context of the QuakeReport app.
请投身于 Quake Report 应用的环境中
Start to imagine what parts of the code need to be moved around or added.
开始构思需要移除 和添加哪些代码
&gt;&gt; You can refer back to the tsunami and digifeel sample apps.
— 你仍然可以参考 Tsunami 和 Digifield 示例应用
&gt;&gt; So think about what the input and
— 因而请思考不同方法的输入
the outputs to the different methods would be.
和输出将是 什么样的
For example, once we parse the JSON response,
例如 在我们解析 JSON 响应时
should the return value still be a single earthquake?
返回值还应是 一次地震吗
What if we want to display a list of earthquakes?
如果我们想要显示 地震列表该怎么办?
&gt;&gt; It's going to be a big coding task with a lot of steps, but
— 这将是一项具有很多步骤的 大型编码任务 但
I'm confident that you can do it.
我相信你能完成它
&gt;&gt; Yeah, totally, go get it.
— 是的 没错 现在开始吧
In this quiz, I want you to go and
在此测验中 我希望你计划一下
plan the changes that you want to make to the Quake Report app.
要对 Quake Report 应用 作出的更改
Go ahead and plan your steps for
继续计划用于
how you'll modify the Quake Report app to perform the network request.
修改 Quake Report 应用以 执行网络请求的步骤
Then list your detailed steps right here.
然后在此列出 详细的步骤